[{"answer": "Well, I'm not sure how important that is.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "Is it time he left the party, do you think?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Well, I think when you have somebody of your own race that you're proud of being president of the United States, I applaud Colin for standing with him.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "What reason would that be?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "This is the time that people should be putting plans together.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "What is your view now about where we are with the information?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "I don't think so, because the storm today, and that's the Twitter universe, that was exactly what I was thinking at that moment in time.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "Is it as dire today as it seemed last night?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "I think it's probably not true.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "Was he just being stupid?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "That it's only because he's black and Colin Powell is liberal.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "What isn't true?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "I agree with the bottom line.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "You actually agree with me?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "I think it's not a racist country.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Is America a more or less racist country since Barack Obama became president?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "I can save you a lot of time.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "You actually believe that?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "For the law, yes.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Is that your belief?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "The latest poll, \"USA Today\"/Gallup says abortion at 39 percent is the number one issue for women in 12 swing states.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "And when you're running for office, will you stop talking philosophically?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "I'm suspicious of that.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "You surprised by that?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think it's much of a threat.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "Would you like Romney if he wins to overturn Roe versus Wade as he has threatened to in the past?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "I think you are doing what you are so testy with Sununu doing to Colin Powell.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "ORGAN: Why did you do it?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "Because it's a synonym for loser.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "Why call the president of the United States a retard?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "OK, it's offensive and you're going to come up with 20 different ways to tell me it's offensive.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Says who?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "Not the \"N\" word argument.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "You wouldn't use the \"N\" word, would you?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "I should have called my book three books back about \"Guilty: Liberal Victims and Their Assault on America\".", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "Why would you allow the word police as you put it to make any exceptions?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "Will you continue using the retard word?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "Yes, of course.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "Yes, it's going to be my exhibit henceforth for both of the groups I want to take the vote away from, young people and women.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "I'm sure you loved that, didn't you?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "You would take away the female vote, would you?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "That it was a rash experiment and we should reconsider the 19th Amendment.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "What is the point?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "Calm down.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "What have I said that's been remotely sexist?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "I think it's going to be Romney.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "Who's going to win the election?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "I like the drone attacks.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "Where do you credit the president?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "I can't say I'm in favor of the withdrawal since I was against the escalation.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "You in favor of that?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "Who is that?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "I'm not pressing buttons.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Why do you press those little buttons?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "Please.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "ORGAN: Do you like being offensive?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "Manifestly not.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "Do you mind that?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "Well, no, to annoy liberals which isn't very hard, by the way.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "A gift to be offensive?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "Would you ever date a liberal?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "Well, the word retard is offensive and should not be -- should not be a symbol for someone who is dumb and shallow.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "What was your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "TEPHENS: I have.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Have you ever met him?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "Do you think there's a wider argument that, putting aside the disability, the word retard, the offense it causes to people like yourself, that actually you should just use more respect to the president?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "I would like to say thank you.", "docId": "121026pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "What would you like to say in conclusion?", "qSentId": 637}]